连读规则三：元音加元音。当一个以元音音结尾的词挨着
Liaison rule three, vowel, vowel. When a word ending in a vowel sound is next to
一个词以元音音开头时，两个词之间会用滑音连接。
one beginning with a vowel sound, they're connected with a glide between the two
滑音是轻微的 Y 音或轻微的 W 音。你怎么知道该用哪一个？
vowels. A glide is either a slight Y sound or a slight W sound. How do you know which
该用哪个？这会自然发生。你的嘴唇位置会决定
one to use? This will take care of itself. The position your lips are in will dictate
是 Y 还是 W。先看两个例子；如果一个词以
either Y or W. Go away, I also need the other one. For example, if a word ends in
O 音时，嘴唇处在前伸位置，所以 W 很自然地会带着声音
O, lips are going to be in the forward position, so a W quite naturally leads
滑进下一个元音音：go away。不要把 go away 说断，破坏元音连接。
into the next vowel sound, go away. You don't want to say go away and break the
声音的底层流动。把它连在一起说：go away。在一个拉长的 E 音之后，
undercurrent of your voice. Run it all together, go away. After a long E sound,
你的嘴唇会向后拉到足以产生 Y 滑音或连读的位置。
your lips will be pulled back far enough to create a Y glide or liaison. I also
need the other one。不要太用力；它其实不是很强的
need the other one. Don't force this too much though. It's not really a strong
推送音。I also need the other one 如果缺少这个推送音，就会听起来很奇怪。
pushing sound. I also need the other one would sound really weird.